https://www.kazlg.com/new-california-privacy-law-ccpa/

Skip to content
New California Law Gives Control Of Personal Information Back To Consumers
The CCPA: A Needed New Protection For California ConsumersAs of January 1st, 2020, California consumers have a powerful new tool to help protect their privacy- the California Consumer Protection Act. Under this new statute, Californians will be able find out exactly what personal information companies have compiled about them, and sue them if that information is stored incorrectly or leaked.The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) is a comprehensive new consumer protection law set to take effect on January 1, 2020 that offers new protections for the personal data of Californians. The CCPA introduces new privacy rights for Californians, such as the right to know what personal information a business has collected about them and the details on how the business uses and discloses the data. Kazerouni Law Group, along with the law firms of Blood Hurst & O’Reardon, LLP and Robinson Calcagnie, Inc, helped draft this groundbreaking new statute, which gives Californians a much needed right of action to defend their privacy.The CCPA gives every Californian the right to demand a full accounting of the information a company has compiled about them, as well as full transparency as to any third parties whom that company may be sharing that data with. In addition, the California law allows consumers to sue companies if the privacy guidelines are violated, even if there is no breach.What Does This Mean For Me?Any company that serves Californian consumers and has annual revenues of $25 million or more must comply with the CCPA. Also, the CCPA regulates any company that keeps personal data on at least 50,000 people, as well as those that collect more than half of their revenues from the sale of personal data. Companies don’t have to be based in California or have a physical presence there to fall under the CCPA. If you believe you have a claim under CCPA, or that your data has been illegally stored or breached, contact the experts at Kazerouni Law Group today.
Locations
Orange County
245 Fischer Avenue Suite D1 Costa Mesa, CA 92626  Phone: 949-612-9999 Fax: 1-800-520-5523 Map & Direction
San Diego
2221 Camino del Rio South Suite 101 San Diego, CA 92108 Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523 Map & Directions
Arroyo Grande
1303 East Grand Avenue Suite 101 Arroyo Grande, CA 93420 Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523 Map & Directions
Minneapolis
120 S. 6th St.,Suite 2050Minneapolis, MN 55402Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
St. George
321 N Mall DriveSuite R108St George, UT  84790Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
Las Vegas
6069 South Fort Apache RoadSuite 100Las Vegas, NV 89148Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
Phoenix
2633 E. Indian School RoadSuite 460Phoenix, AZ 85016Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
Dallas
1910 Pacific AveSuite 14155Dallas, TX 75201Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
Washington
5608 17th Avenue NW #891Seattle, Washington 98107Phone: 1-800-778-2065Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
New York City
275 Seventh Avenue7th FloorNew York, NY 10001Phone: 1-800-400-6808Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
New Jersey
3000 Atrium Way Suite 200 Mt. Laurel , NJ 08054Phone: 1-800-400-6808Fax: 1-800-520-5523Map & Directions
Contact Us | Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | Accessibility Statement | Site Map
Copyright © 2020 Kazerouni Law Group, APC. All Rights Reserved | Website by Advocate Media Company, Inc.
Call Now
Email Us
Scroll to Top
